LUKA RAKOCEVIC



Contact

Address:

Petra Lekovica 6, Belgrade, Serbia

Phone:

061/166-59-30

Email:

dr.dexxter@gmail.com

Languages

English – C2 German – A2

Summary

Seasoned office manager and a great team player. Experienced with all day-to-day company activities. Well-versed in planning activities, workforce management, scheduling tasks. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Education

Bachelor of Economics: 2009, Megatrend university

Certifications

- * Very proficient in MS Office Word, Excell, Access, Outlook, Powerpoint
- * Experienced in hardware assembly, management and installation, as well as troubleshooting
- * Extensive know-how in installing and maintaining Windows OS platforms, as well as troubleshooting and problem solving
- * Knowlegde of Joomla and Wordpress CMS, Vinca institute certificate
- * Knowledge of database management systems such as MySQL, MS Access and Oracle
- * Knowledge of Javascript, HTML5/CSS3

LUKA RAKOCEVIC

Work Experience

Field Operations Manager – May 2022 – ongoing Edge Technologies d.o.o.

- managing incoming calls, emails, and chats from prospective clients
- managing outbound calls and digital communications to close new business
- managing field and sales staff to facilitate successful completion of sale
- managing appointments and calendars for new clientele
- expanding and extend expertise to build strong healthy and trusting relationships with sales staff and new clients
- conveying the benefit of doing business with the organization
- fostering an environment of open and accessible communication
- meeting or exceeding company sales goals and key metrics

Call center agent first line – May 2021 – January 2022 Hyperoptic LLC, UK

- offering first line assistance to customers with queries
- maintaining clear, accurate customer records, update database records upon request
- work out billing issues with customers
- keep track of connection faults, outages, inform customers accordingly
- Perform service activations
- troubleshoot with customers in case of connection issues
- help customers open up new accounts
- own customer enquires / issues till completion

Office manager – October 2016 – May 2021 Extreme Media DOO

- uploading, keywording, writing descriptions of photographs for stock photography websites iStock and Getty images
- coordinating the workflow of retouches and quality control
- controlling the batch upload volume based on current trends, independent decision-making
- content-writing and web maintenance activities for the following company websites:

http://www.extreme-photographer.com http://www.extremecanyoning.com https://www.montenegrobook.com

LUKA RAKOCEVIC

Work Experience

- photography scouting and on-site coordination during photo shooting
- translation services for publishing purposes
- daily activity schedule-making and maintaining the company workflow
- receiving and filing invoices for the accounting department, assembling, printing and sending invoices to the company clients and partners
- procurement of office supplies
- daily communication with company clients by phone and email
- keeping books on company accounts and paying bills

Call center agent first line – September 2015 – March 2016 Sitel SBA d.o.o, Amazon campaign

- customer communication via VoiP phone and emails
- cooperation with various courier services (Hermes, UPS, DHL) and providing feedback to customers
- payment control, payment method, and customer account control
- exposing potential fraud and other malicious activities
- providing help with payment problems or payment methods
- control of content on the website
- tracking shipments, resolving cases of missing parcels
- providing all the necessary information to users related to any aspect of Amazon's store

English translator – September 2014– ongoing **Laguna d.o.o.**

- translating various non-published texts submitted by thirdparty
- helping in published translations and providing proofing assistance